{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "import React from 'react'\nimport { useState, useEffect ,useCallback} from 'react'\nimport './trip-list.css'\n\nexport default function TripList() {\nconst [trips, setTrips] = useState([])\nconst [url, setUrl]= useState('http://localhost:3000/trips')\nconst fetchTrips = useCallback (async () => {\n\tconst response = await fetch(url)\n\tconst json = await response.json()\n\tsetTrips(json)\n},[url])\n\nuseEffect(() = {\n\tfetchTrips()\n}, [url, fetchTrips])\n\nconsole.log(trips)",
      "statement": "error: Expression expected in useffect",
      "answers": ["()=>", "Function() ={}", "() {}", "Function={}"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "import React, { useState } from 'react';\n\nconst App = () => {\n\tconst [count, setCount] = useState(0);\n\nreturn (\n\t<div>\n\t\t<p>The count is {count}</p>\n\t\t<button onClick={() => setCount(count + 1)}>Increment</button>\n\t\t</div>\n\t);\n};\n\nexport default App;",
      "statement": "What is the error?",
      "answers": [
        "The useState hook is not imported correctly",
        "The setCount function is not updating the state properly",
        "The count state is not being passed to the setCount function as an argument",
        "There is no error in the code."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "import React, { useState } from 'react';\n\nconst App = () => {\n\tconst [state, setState] = useState({\n\t\tname: '',\n\t\temail: '',\n\t});\n\tconst handleChange = (event) => {\n\t\tsetState({\n\t\t\t...state,\n\t\t\t[event.target.name]: event.target.value,\n\t\t});\n\t};\n\treturn (\n\t\t<form>\n\t\t\t<input type=\"text\" name=\"name\" onChange={handleChange} />\n\t\t\t<input type=\"email\" name=\"email\" onChange={handleChange} />\n\t\t</form>\n\t);\n};\n\nexport default App;",
      "statement": "What is the error?",
      "answers": [
        "The handleChange function is not updating the state properly",
        "The name and email properties in the state object are not correctly being updated in the handleChange function",
        "The handleChange function is not being passed to the input elements as the onChange prop",
        "There is no error in the code."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "void main() => runApp(MyApp());\n\nclass MyApp extends StatelessWidget {\n\t@override\n\tWidget build(BuildContext context) {\n\t\treturn MaterialApp(\n\t\t\thome: Scaffold(\n\t\t\t\tbody: Center(\n\t\t\t\t\tchild: Text('Hello World'),\n\t\t\t\t),\n\t\t\t),\n\t\t);\n\t}\n}",
      "statement": "What is the output of the following asynchronous Dart code?",
      "answers": [
        "The Scaffold widget is not imported correctly",
        "The Text widget does not have any text to display",
        "Package Problem",
        "The runApp method is not being passed the MyApp widget"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "interface A\n{\nprivate int i;\n}",
      "statement": "Identify the error in the following code:",
      "answers": [
        "Variables cannot be declared in an interface, only methods.",
        "Variables can be declared, but they can only be public.",
        "Variables declared must be initialised.",
        "Both (b) and (c)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "#include<iostream>\nusing namespace std;\n\nclass Test{\nstatic int i;\nint j;\n};\n\nint Test::i;\n\nint main(){\ncout << sizeof(Test);\nreturn 0;\n}",
      "statement": "What is the output of the code?",
      "answers": ["4", "6", "8", "Code will not compile."],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "# Program to check if 'a' is greater than or equal to 'b'\na = 25\nb = 20\nif a => b:\nprint(\"a is greater!\")",
      "statement": "Debug the following Python code:",
      "answers": [
        "Exclamatory mark (!) cannot be used in print statement.",
        "Indentation is not correct.",
        "Incorrect use of comparison operator.",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "const oneSecond = Duration(seconds: 1);\nFuture<void> printWithDelay(String message) async {\nawait Future.delayed(oneSecond);\nprint(message);\n}\n\nvoid main(){\nprintWithDelay(\"Ambiora\");\nprint(\"Techfest\");\n}",
      "statement": "What is the output of the following asynchronous Dart code?",
      "answers": [
        "Ambiora\nTechfest",
        "Techfest\nAmbiora",
        "AmbioraTechfest",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "import 'package:flutter/material.dart';\n\nvoid main() => runApp(MyApp());\n\nclass MyApp extends StatelessWidget {\n\t@override\n\tWidget build(BuildContext context) {\n\t\treturn MaterialApp(\n\t\t\thome: Scaffold(\n\t\t\t\tbody: Center(\n\t\t\t\t\tchild: Column(\n\t\t\t\t\t\tmainAxisAlignment: MainAxisAlignment.center,\n\t\t\t\t\t\tchildren: <Widget>[\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\tText(\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t'You have pushed the button this many times:',\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t),\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\tText(\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t'$_counter',\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tstyle: Theme.of(context).textTheme.headline4,\n\t\t\t\t\t\t\t),\n\t\t\t\t\t\t],\n\t\t\t\t\t),\n\t\t\t\t),\n\t\t\t\tfloatingActionButton: FloatingActionButton(\n\t\t\t\t\tonPressed: _incrementCounter,\n\t\t\t\t\ttooltip: 'Increment',\n\t\t\t\t\tchild: Icon(Icons.add),\n\t\t\t\t),\n\t\t\t),\n\t\t);\n\t}\n}",
      "statement": "What is the error?",
      "answers": [
        "The FloatingActionButton widget is not imported correctly",
        "The _incrementCounter function is not updating the state properly",
        "The setState method is not being passed a function to update the _counter variable",
        "Wrong implementation of stateless widget"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "def func(x, ans):\n\tif(x==0):\n\t\treturn 0\n\telse:\n\t\treturn func(x-1, x+ans)\nprint(func(2,0))",
      "statement": "What is the output of the following Python code?",
      "answers": ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "#include<iostream>\n\nusing namespace std;\nmain() {\n\tint r, x = 2;\n\n\tfloat y = 5;\n\n\tr = y%x;\n\tcout<<r;\n}",
      "statement": "What is the output of the following C++ code?",
      "answers": ["1", "0", "2", "Compile error"],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "#include<stdio.h>\nmain()\n{\nint i;\nchar s[] = \"hello\";\nfor(i=0; s[i]; ++i);\nprintf(\"%d \", i);\ni=0;\nwhile(s[i++]);\nprintf(\"%d \", i);\n}",
      "statement": "Does both the loops in the following programs prints the correct string length?",
      "answers": [
        "Yes, both the loops print the correct string length.",
        "Only for loop prints the correct length",
        "Only while loop prints the correct length",
        "Compile error in the program"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "class A: \n\tdef __init__(self, i=100): \n\t\tself.i=i \nclass B(A): \n\tdef __init__(self,j=0): \n\t\tself.j=j \ndef main(): \n\tb= B() \n\tprint(b.i) \n\tprint(b.j) \nmain()",
      "statement": "What happens in the below code?",
      "answers": [
        "Class B inherits all the data fields of class A.",
        "Class B needs an Argument.",
        "The data field ‘j’ cannot be accessed by object b.",
        "Class B is inheriting class A but the data field ‘i’ in A cannot be inherited."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "#include<stdio.h>\n#include<stdlib.h>\n#define MAXROW 4\n# define MAXCOL 5\nint main ()\n{\nint **p, i, j\np = (int **) malloc(MAXROW * sizeof(int*));\nreturn 0;\n}",
      "statement": "The given below program allocates the memory, what function will you use to free the allocated memory?",
      "answers": [
        "memfree(int p);",
        "free(p);",
        "dealloc(p);",
        "Both, free(p); & dealloc(p);"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "int main()\n{\nint arr[] = {4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13};\nint *p = (arr + 1);\ncout << *arr + 9;\nreturn 0;\n}",
      "statement": "What is the output of the following C++ code?",
      "answers": ["9", "13", "22", "error"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "class Test\n{\n\tpublic static void main (String[] args) \n\t{\n\t\tint arr1[] = {1, 2, 3};\n\t\tint arr2[] = {1, 2, 3};\n\t\tif (arr1 == arr2) \n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(\"Same\");\n\t\telse\n\t\t\tSystem.out.println(\"Not same\");\n\t}\n}",
      "statement": "What is the output of the following Java code?",
      "answers": ["Same", "Not same", "Compile error", "Runtime error"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "int multiplyRec(int m, int n)\n{\n\tif(n == 1)\n\t\treturn m;\n\treturn m + multiplyRec(m,  n - 1);\n}",
      "statement": "What is the Time Complexity of the following recursive function?",
      "answers": ["O(m*n)", "O(n)", "O(n^2)", "O(m)"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "def f():\n\ta = 0\n\tfor i in range(1, n):\n\t\ta += random.randint()\n\t\tb = 0\n\t\tfor j in range(1, m):\n\t\t\tb += random.randint()",
      "statement": "What is the Time Complexity of the following recursive function?",
      "answers": ["O(n)", "O(m)", "O(n+m)", "O(n*m)"],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "randomList = ['a',2,3]\nfor element in randomList:\n\tprint('The Element is ',element)\n\tx=int(element + 1)\n\tprint('The Increment of ',element,'is',x)",
      "statement": "Which of the following Error will be raised by the Given Python Code?",
      "answers": ["NameError", "ValueError", "TypeError", "IOError"],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "int main()\n{\n\tint a[5] = {7, 21, 18, 26, 31};\n\tint i, j, m;\n\tfor(i=0;i<4;i++)\n\t{\n\t\t++a[i];\n\t\ta[i+1]++;\n\t\ta[i++];\n\t\tcout<<a[i];\n\t}\n\treturn 0;\n}",
      "statement": "What is the output of the following C++ code?",
      "answers": ["2227", "2227992", "8221", "8221992"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "#include<iostream>\nusing namespace std;\nint main (){\nif (!(cout << \"Techfest\" ) )\ncout << \"Ambiora\";\nelse\ncout << \" 2023\";\nreturn 0;\n}",
      "statement": "What is the output of the following C++ code?",
      "answers": ["2023", "Ambiora 2023", "Techfest 2023", "Techfest"],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "#include<iostream>\nusing namespace std;\nint N=25;\nint main(){\nstatic int a=15;\na++;\nif(cout<<a<<\" \"&&a++<N&&main())\n{}\nreturn 0;\n}",
      "statement": "What is the output of the following C++ code?",
      "answers": [
        "15 16 17 18 19 20 21",
        "15 17 19 21",
        "16 18 20 22",
        "16 18 20"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    }
  ]
}
